hey what's up everybody thanks for
listening to The Grow Your Life podcast
my name is Jeremy Gronkowski and I want
to talk about how you can get more
clients in your coaching business today
that's the goal of this podcast it's the
goal of what we do in our business is to
help you get more clients the number one
thing that most people Miss is they
don't have a high impact offer they
don't have an offer that people actually
care about and their messaging isn't
matching what people actually want now
truthfully I think that people need to
get rid of one-on-one coaching in their
business they need to do group coaching
but because you're able to leverage your
time without getting overwhelmed and
you're able to reach and impact more
people but how do you put an offer
together that people actually want well
last week we did a podcast all about the
feedback loop in your business go take a
listen to that all about the feedback
loop once you identify the feedback loop
you have to create offers that deliver
value to people and how we do that is
with virtual events over Zoom we do
virtual Zoom events we're hosting a
five-day intensive next week where I'm
going to walk you through how to grow
your coaching business with live virtual
Zoom events you can find that over at
jeremicarkowski.com where I'm going to
help you do that we're going to map out
your virtual event process for you how
do virtual events work and why are they
so effective as offers first off you
might be like well all I want to do is I
just want to send people to my coaching
program and have them sign up as a
client that might have worked back five
years ago it doesn't work anymore and so
virtual events serve for this purpose
they build trust with your client they
give you an opportunity to demonstrate
how well you are as a coach and they
allow you to connect with the right
people that are meant to work with you
in your business and they do so in a way
that's one to many not just one-to-one
it also allows you to facilitate the
feedback loop essentially you're able to
bribe people who show up for your
virtual event to tell you what they're
struggling with what they want to learn
and create that feedback loop now the
other thing I want to tell you is your
offer needs to be priced enough so that
you can actually make the kind of money
that's possible in your coaching
business
might be like well I just want to be the
cheapest option so I can impact more
people you're not going to impact more
people that way you need to charge at
least
three hundred dollars minimum in the
beginning and all the way up to I would
recommend a thousand dollars minimum for
most people as their offers
and so what we do is this we do a
virtual event on Zoom where people
listen
and they get skill set and they get
trained on how to do certain things such
as growing their email list or getting
new clients with paid ads or how to plan
out their signature coaching program
like we're hosting on Tuesday this
coming week as well and we we deliver on
that promise we actually give that value
that's important you're not going to
build trust with people it was just a
bait and switch so you gotta actually
give value to people
and then at the end of it you make an
offer for something for people to sign
up for to purchase with you now will
everybody purchase no of course not but
you will expose yourself to the right
people that are meant to work with you
by doing this over time and what we
found is some people like they might
come in for one virtual event and by
event number five they become a client
and so it takes about five interactions
to really convert people to a sale when
they first find us and so that's why
we're constantly doing events each month
to connect with people if you if you
don't get a chance to register for the
ones that we got going on this week
register for the ones that are upcoming
and what you're going to do is this
you're going to learn the strategies I'm
going to teach them to you you're also
going to watch How I do my sales pitch
how I sell to people how I close the
room okay and so it's one to two-fold
you can learn by watching somebody who's
been in the industry for 20 years get
better at it by seeing how it works how
all the pieces work together and then
you do your own virtual event to get
clients there's a structure when it
comes to Virtual events
the structure is this
and I've only ever given this away to my
highest level coaching group now I'm
giving it away to my podcast for free
you might be like wow they if I get this
for free what does the coaching group
get well they get they get guidance and
support to make multiple six and seven
figures and so this is the foundation of
it is running virtual events that work
this way so you want to script your
event out
to where the first 33 percent of the the
event that you do whether it be a
webinar whether it be a five-day
challenge
is all based on
mindset
what is the mindset that you're trying
to help your clients with
what is the mindset that you're walking
people through
you you
reframe and you recast the vision that
they have
you remind them of the reason why they
registered in the first place and this
does twofold a it's going to piss off a
lot of people that aren't a good fit for
you as a client they'll leave you well I
don't want to piss anybody off well yeah
you're going to anger some people and
here's why because they're going to feel
like you wasted their time by just
talking about mindset and vision well
those negative nancies you don't want
around you and they're not going to buy
from you anyways they're just looking
for a reason to criticize you and
disqualify you and discredit you that's
what I found is by doing mindset in the
very first beginning part of our event
the first 33 we really focus in on
mindset
we're able to repel the people that
aren't a good fit to work with us in our
business and then we're able to attract
the ones that actually get results
because they have a vision they resonate
with that what's cool is what you're
doing is you're imparting Faith to
People by giving them that mindset now
in the middle 33 to 50 portion of the
event
we talk about the promised
training okay so like
the the actual promised training of why
people are going to attend the event is
given during that middle portion right
there where we walk them through the
strategies and the the technical aspect
and and we walk them through step by
step and then the last portion is where
you do your sales pitch at the very end
33 of it you sell
you might be like why cringe at sales I
think sales is disgusting and gross
here's the thing
maybe you experience cringy salespeople
nobody who listens to me sell says that
I'm cringy so
a way to do it that's that's cringy and
there's a way to do it it's not
and that's what that's what I'm going to
show you on the five-day event that
we're doing that's what we work with our
coaching clients through is how to sell
without being cringe
how to sell without being yuck okay
because here's the thing if you have the
confidence to know that when I run a
virtual event
I can close sales you're going to do it
every single month and that's going to
make you a millionaire
I'm on a mission to make over a thousand
people in the millionaires as coaches in
their business
I know I can do it
but it takes
finding those people first off and then
walking them through a proven process
and so that's what I do that's what this
podcast says that's why we have over a
thousand videos on our YouTube channel
is to walk you through the proven
process
to make more money in your coaching
business to get those results that
you're looking for to get those results
that you're hoping and praying for
instead of struggling and wondering how
am I going to make all this work
you don't have to struggle anymore
you don't have to strive
you don't have to wonder what should I
say on my landing page what should I say
in my offer how do I build out a funnel
how do I actually get people to sign up
with me
that's what I teach you we teach you
strategies for finding clients and
closing sales
we find them and then we close them or
we keep them on our list we keep them on
our list and we keep emailing people and
you want to email your list every single
day well what if they unsubscribe great
let them unsubscribe
because it's actually better if they do
unsubscribe instead of staying on your
list and taking up space and and
contributing to your unopened rate
we have industry High open rates for our
emails 60 to 70 percent of everybody we
send an email to opens an email because
we remove the people or we encourage
them to remove themselves from our list
by emailing them every single day and
that strategy that's that's one of the
million dollar strategies million dollar
coaches are not afraid to bother their
list
and so this is why your mindset and how
you think about business well am I
confident enough am I good enough I
don't want to bother people I don't want
to be a cringy salesperson you gotta
shift your self-perception
how you see yourself how you perceive
yourself your judgments that you have
towards salespeople
the judgments that you have towards
people that sell and shift into
an abundance mindset this isn't woo-woo
this is literally you seeing yourself
producing a quarter of a million dollars
in sales half a million dollars in sales
seven figures in sales
visualize yourself accomplishing
what it is that you're setting out to do
it starts by having a vision
believing the vision and then selling
that Vision to people on social media
well that's just not my personality okay
great you can grow in the skill set it
wasn't my personality either and this is
why I stress this a lot if I could do it
you can too
because I sucked at this stuff when I
started I was terrible at it I didn't
know how to communicate very well
I didn't know how to do all this and you
don't have to do over 200 podcast
episodes to get better at it
we got tools now that you can use chat
GPT is absolutely incredible at
processing the feedback loop and turning
it into killer marketing campaigns and
so listen I'd love to work with you
consider joining the waiting list for my
client growth accelerator we're
considering changing the name of it
possible name change might be the
wealthy coach Academy so if it's called
that in the future or something else
it's a group coaching program where we
work with you through
the challenges in your business to help
you get wealthy and make as much money
as possible in your coaching business
I'm on a mission to make you rich and
I'm gonna do it
or you're not going to listen to me
anymore you're not gonna because you're
gonna go on some other direction
and so thanks for being here keep
plugging in we'll talk soon everybody
have a good one